LaForce, Martin Papers 5439
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Martin LaForce Papers
1918-1965
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
LaForce, Martin
5439
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
Background material for a Ph.D. dissertation on labor education at Syracuse University, 1966, titled "Labour and Education in England."
5650553
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 03, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 12, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Laforce, Martin.
5650553
- Background material for a Ph.D. dissertation on labor education at Syracuse University, 1966, titled Labour and Education in England.. (Box 1)
  - Union Booklets & "12 Wasted Years, 1923-1964 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Union Articles & Booklets, 1918-1965 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - National Union of Teachers, 1922-1943 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Background material for a Ph.D. dissertation on labor education at Syracuse University, 1966, titled Labour and Education in England.. (Box 2)
  - Lg Ed. Memoes. 19-10-1, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Memoes Ad hoc. Com., 1950-1951 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Numerous notes from Marty, 1953-1956 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Ed. RAR 1947-1949 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - RAR Memo - '53-'55, 1953-1955 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Memos: Ed. Rdu. Com. 1941-4, 1941-1944 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Memos: Ed. Rdu. Com. 1941-4, 1941-1944 (Box 2, Folder 7)